var quiz = [
  {
    uniqueID: 1,
    question: "Who shot first Han Solo or Greedo",
    options: ["Han Solo", "Greedo"],
    answer: "Han Solo"
  },
  {
    uniqueID: 2,
    question: "What is the name of the first ewok Princess Leia encounters on Endoor?",
    options: ["Teek", "Wicket", "Weedee", "Nubnub"],
    answer: "Wicket"
  },
  {
    uniqueID: 3,
    question: "What is the name the spaceship captained by Han Solo?",
    options: ["X-wing", "Y-wing", "Milenium Eagle", "Milenium Falcon"],
    answer: "Milenium Falcon"
  },
  {
    uniqueID: 4,
    question: "What is the name of the Bounty Hunter that captures Han Solo",
    options: ["Jango Fett", "IG-88", "Boba Fett"],
    answer: "Boba Fett"
  },
  {
    uniqueID: 5,
    question: "If [4]*[4] = 16, what will [4, 4]*[4, 4] equal?",
    options: ["[16, 16]", "[64, 64]", "NaN", "[[4, 4], [4, 4], [4, 4], [4,4]]"],
    answer: "NaN"
  },
  {
    uniqueID: 6,
    question: "var nums = [1, 2, 3];<br>nums.splice(nums.indexOf(('wtf'), 1);<br>What is nums?",
    options: ["[1, 2, 3]", "NaN", "[]", "[1, 2]"],
    answer: "[1, 2]"
  },
  {
    uniqueID: 7,
    question: "True Story Bro<br>'true' == true?",
    options: ["true", "false"],
    answer: "false"
  },
  {
    uniqueID: 8,
    question: "var nums = [1, 2, 3];<br>nums.splice(nums.indexOf(('wtf'), 1);<br>What is nums?",
    options: ["[1, 2, 3]", "NaN", "[]", "[1, 2]"],
    answer: "[1, 2]"
  },
  {
    uniqueID: 9,
    question: "var nums = [1, 2, 3];<br>nums.splice(nums.indexOf(('wtf'), 1);<br>What is nums?",
    options: ["[1, 2, 3]", "NaN", "[]", "[1, 2]"],
    answer: "[1, 2]"
  },
  {
    uniqueID: 10,
    question: "var nums = [1, 2, 3];<br>nums.splice(nums.indexOf(('wtf'), 1);<br>What is nums?",
    options: ["[1, 2, 3]", "NaN", "[]", "[1, 2]"],
    answer: "[1, 2]"
  },
  {
    uniqueID: 11,
    question: "var nums = [1, 2, 3];<br>nums.splice(nums.indexOf(('wtf'), 1);<br>What is nums?",
    options: ["[1, 2, 3]", "NaN", "[]", "[1, 2]"],
    answer: "[1, 2]"
  }

];
